<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>JeremyandDarcy.com</title>
    <link>http://jeremyanddarcy.com</link>
    <pubDate>2013-06-08 11:04:31 -0400</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Preparation For The Journey</title>
      <link>http://jeremyanddarcy.com/preparation-for-the-journey</link>
      <pubDate>2013-06-07</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s some photos of all the prep work going into the trip. Darcy made activity bins for Madeleine, Nena and Eloise, which the
girls decorated themselves.  We bought a &lt;a href="http://waterstep.org"&gt;WaterStep&lt;/a&gt; cup for everyone in the family, so each of us have
a reusable cup for the trip, and someone, somewhere, will have cleaner water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Packing the RV has been an exercise in efficiency! But I think we have found a place for everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;embed type="application/x-shockwave-flash" src="https://static.googleusercontent.com/external_content/picasaweb.googleusercontent.com/slideshow.swf" width="400" height="267" flashvars="host=picasaweb.google.com&amp;hl=en_US&amp;feat=flashalbum&amp;RGB=0x000000&amp;feed=https%3A%2F%2Fpicasaweb.google.com%2Fdata%2Ffeed%2Fapi%2Fuser%2F116065733838856651489%2Falbumid%2F5886594153184555985%3Falt%3Drss%26kind%3Dphoto%26authkey%3DGv1sRgCOSQ6K3FjeShfg%26hl%3Den_US" pluginspage="http://www.macromedia.com/go/getflashplayer"&gt;&lt;/embed&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Running After One's Hat</title>
      <link>http://jeremyanddarcy.com/on-running-after-one-s-hat</link>
      <pubDate>2013-06-05</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m amused by the reactions I get when people hear that we&amp;#39;re taking an RV on a 5 week trip. 
It&amp;#39;s always a binary response. Either it&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;Wow that&amp;#39;s going to be so awesome!&amp;quot;. 
Or it&amp;#39;s, &amp;quot;Are you out of your mind? 3 kids in 170 square feet of RV for 5 weeks!?&amp;quot;. Honestly, I frequently ask myself the same thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regardless of which way they respond, I am reminded of one of my favorite G.K. Chesterton quotes,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;An adventure is only an inconvenience rightly considered. An inconvenience is only an adventure wrongly considered.&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This quote comes from G.K. Chesterton&amp;#39;s &lt;a href="http://www.gutenberg.org/ebooks/11505"&gt;&amp;quot;All Things Considered&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt; in a brilliant chapter titled 
&lt;a href="http://www.catholic-forum.com/saints/gkc16004.htm"&gt;&amp;quot;On Running After One&amp;#39;s Hat&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of Darcy&amp;#39;s mentors in college is known for saying 
&lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;You control the environment which in turn controls you&amp;quot;.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the book &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/The-Art-Possibility-Transforming-Professional/dp/0142001104/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1370469387&amp;amp;sr=8-1&amp;amp;keywords=art+of+possibility"&gt;&amp;quot;The Art of Possibility&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;
, the authors write:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;Every problem, every dilemma, every dead end we find ourselves facing in life, only appears unsolvable inside
a particular frame or point of view.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s secret about life that is unraveled for us in this idea: Life is all about how we perceive it, and that determines 
how we react to it. We can&amp;#39;t control what life throws at us, but &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; control how we react to it. How we react to it is what everyone 
else sees, and how we remember it, and how we choose whether it&amp;#39;s a &amp;quot;good thing&amp;quot; or a &amp;quot;bad thing&amp;quot;. This, in my opinion, 
makes &amp;quot;what happened&amp;quot; insignificant in comparison to &amp;quot;what we did about it&amp;quot;. Life is defined by our experiences, and
we get to define the experience as bad or good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are we crazy to do this? YES! Is it going to be uncomfortable? YES! Is it going to be awesome still? YES! Is it going to be something our girls remember the rest of their lives? YES!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do I make certain that when they look back on it 20 years from now, they remember it as one of the greatest summers of their life, regardless 
of what trouble we run into? I think the secret is in how we frame every moment.  The girls are young, and I think they
frame life mostly based on how they see Darcy and I framing life. Anybody who has kids know&amp;#39;s how humbling it is to see yourself
reflected in how they react to situations both in action and in words. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the motto for this trip is Chesteron&amp;#39;s quote:
&lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;An adventure is only an inconvenience rightly considered. An inconvenience is only an adventure wrongly considered.&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;#39;s exactly how we will make this trip awesome, we will &amp;quot;rightly consider&amp;quot; every &amp;quot;inconvenience&amp;quot; so that in the end we
remember it all as an &amp;quot;adventure&amp;quot;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
